stpwebhosting.com 2008-09-17

# STP Web Hosting: Privacy Policy

| 

**Privacy Policy**

**Content:**

It is the information which is provided by the user for various purposes and collected by us when: 

(1) A client signs up for any Webhosting plan or product from our site;   
(2) He submits his request for domain name registration;  
(3) He provides his feedback through prescribed form or mail;  
(4) He raises a support ticket;  
(5) He requests us to provide him technical assistance to resolve his website problem;   
(6) He registers himself to our forum for keeping himself updated with current happenings in Webhosting;   
(7) he approaches our technical team through live chat to obtain technical support;  
(8) He approaches us through telephone to obtain technical support;  
(9) we take back up of your data on our server; etc. etc. 

**Correctness of Client information :**

We collect client's information under assumption that the client is providing necessary information knowing his legal obligation about the correctness of the information. Under all circumstances the information shall not:

(1) Be false, misleading, inaccurate or fraudulent;  
(2) Infringe any third party's copyright, patent, trademark, trade secret or other proprietary rights; or any other rights;   
(3) Violate any law, statute, ordinance or law;   
(4) Be defamatory, unlawfully threatening or unlawfully harassing,   
(5) Be obscene, offensive, contain any pornography or any other illegal materials;   
(6) Contain any viruses, Trojan Horses, worms, cancel bots or any other computer programming routines that are intended to damage, detrimentally interfere with, surreptitiously intercept any system, data or personal system,   
(7) Create liability for us or cause us to loose (in whole or in part) the services of our ISP or the other suppliers,   
(8) Pretend to be any person or entity, or falsely state or otherwise pretend your affiliation with anyone or anything; 

**How do we use the information?**

1\. Carry out and process financial transactions; during various financial transactions the information are provided to different payment gateways viz. LinkPointCentral.com, Verisign.com, 2checkout.com, BluePay.com; 

2\. Provide technical assistance upon their written or telephonic requests; during such interaction information are provided to our technical and billing personnel who have signed-up the Intellectual Property Right Agreement with us and are bound to follow our Privacy Policy; 3\. Complete the registration formalities with hosting registrar; here some information like name, address, phone numbers, IP Address, etc., are made available for public access through WHOIS report as per the mandatory requirement of domain name registration process; 

**Divulgence of Information :**

Our client should note that in the following exceptions we may divulge the information;

1.1 To an intended recipient of such information which also includes third parties like 2Checkout, VeriSign, BluePay etc, who are payment gateways and operating independently. They are compliant to carry out financial transactions and they follow their own privacy policies over which we do not have any control;  
1.2 With a lawful consent of originator;  
1.3 To a person authorized to provide technical assistance to our clients;   
1.4 To a law enforcement agency as the case may be;   
1.5 To a Domain Name Registrar;

**Client Confirmation :**

To enable STPWebhosting.com to use the information supplied such that we are not violating any rights you might have in that information you agree to grant STPWebhosting.com a non exclusive, worldwide, perpetual, irrevocable, and the rights to sub-license (through multiple tiers) to use the copyrights, publicity and the intellectual property rights you have in the provided information in any media now known and not currently known. STPWebHosting only use that information strictly in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

**Security of client information that we maintain :**

We take every best possible measure to provide the highest protection to our client information on our system. However, we can not guarantee that the information submitted, maintained on and transmitted from our system will be completely secured. In spite of all our security measures we can not rule out the possibility that such information/data could be illegally obtained / destroyed / damaged by some intruder/hacker. In any such event STPWebhosting.com will not hold any liability thereof.

**Changes in Privacy Policy :**

STPWebhosting.com may modify and/or update this Privacy Policy as per the requirement at any time. In case of any major change, we will notify you by placing a notice on our site.
